payprop.com 2019-12-30

# Privacy Policy | PayProp

### We ("Humanstate") operate several websites including payprop.com. It is Humanstate's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

#### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Humanstate collects non-personally identifiable information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Humanstate's purpose in collecting non-personally identifiable information is to better understand how Humanstate's visitors use its website. From time to time, Humanstate may release non-personally identifiable information in aggregate, e.g. by publishing a report on website usage trends. 

Humanstate also collects potentially personally identifiable information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Humanstate does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally identifiable information, as described below. 

#### Gathering of Personally Identifiable Information

Certain visitors to Humanstate's websites choose to interact with Humanstate in ways that require Humanstate to gather personally identifiable information. The amount and type of information that Humanstate gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for our services to provide a username and email address. 

Those who engage in transactions with Humanstate are asked to provide additional information, including the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Humanstate collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Humanstate. Humanstate does not disclose personally identifiable information other than as described below. 

Visitors can always refuse to supply personally identifiable information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

#### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us via the Contact Us link. 

#### Aggregated Statistics

Humanstate may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, we may monitor the most popular service accounts on the Humanstate site. Humanstate may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Humanstate does not disclose personally identifiable information other than as described below. 

#### Protection of Certain Personally Identifiable Information

Humanstate discloses potentially personally identifiable information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that:

  1. need to know that information in order to process it on Humanstate's behalf or to provide services available at Humanstate's websites, and
  2. have agreed not to disclose it to others.

Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country. By using Humanstate's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. 

Humanstate will not rent or sell personally identifiable or potentially personally identifiable information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Humanstate discloses personally identifiable and potentially personally identifiable information only when required to do so by law, or when Humanstate believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Humanstate, third parties or the public at large. 

If you are a registered user of a Humanstate website and have supplied your email address, Humanstate may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or provide updates on Humanstate and our services. 

If you send us a request (for example via a support email or one of our other feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to it, or to help us support other users. 

Humanstate takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

#### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Humanstate uses cookies to help Humanstate identify and track visitors, their usage of the Humanstate website, and their website access preferences. Humanstate visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Humanstate's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Humanstate's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

#### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set their own cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement in order to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Humanstate and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

#### Privacy Policy Changes

Humanstate may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, at Humanstate's sole discretion. Although most changes are likely to be minor, Humanstate encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a payprop.com account, you should also check your account dashboard for alerts regarding these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of said change.
